Guide to the Richard Hell Papers 1944-2003 (Bulk 1969-2003) MSS.140
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Subseries A: Paper Correspondence
    - Quinn, Linda, undated (Box 7, Folder 439)
    - Quiros, Dagmar, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 440)
    - Rainey, Blair, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 441)
    - Ramirez, Jacki, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 442)
    - Ramming, Jet-te L., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 443)
    - Randall, Jim, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 444)
    - Ray, Bryan, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 445)
    - Reed, Jeremy, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 446)
    - Reeves, Rhonda, undated (Box 7, Folder 447)
    - Relativity Records, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 448)
    - Ricard, Rene, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 449)
    - Rickert, Paul, undated (Box 7, Folder 450)
    - Riviera, Jake (Stiff Records), undated (Box 7, Folder 451)
    - Rivera, Tony, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 452)
    - Robble, Andrew, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 453)
    - Robson, Bill, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 454)
    - Rosco, Jerry (Rosco Records), 1980 (Box 7, Folder 455)
    - Rose, Cynthia, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 456)
    - Rose, Joel and Catherine Texier, undated (Box 7, Folder 457)
    - Rosenthal, Bob, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 458)
    - Rossi, Jeri-Cain, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 459)
    - Roth, Henry, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 460)
    - Rower, Ann, 1980-2002 (Box 7, Folder 461)
    - RPM Distributors, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 462)
    - Saroyan, William, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 463)
    - Sato, Yuko, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 464)
    - Satoh, Gin, undated (Box 7, Folder 465)
    - Saunders, Ben, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 466)
    - Schuchat, Simon (to), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 467)
    - Schuchat, Simon (to), 1971 (Box 7, Folder 468)
    - Schuchat, Simon (from), 1971 (Box 7, Folder 469)
    - Schuchat, Simon (to), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 470)
    - Schuchat, Simon (from), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 471)
    - Schuchat, Simon (from), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 472)
    - Schuchat, Simon (to), 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 473)
    - Schuchat, Simon (from), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 474)
    - Schwartz, Andy (NY Rocker), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 475)
    - Schwarz, Sarah, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 476)
    - Scully, Sheilah, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 477)
    - Seideman, Susan, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 478)
    - Sempel, Peter, undated (Box 7, Folder 479)
    - Serlen, Bruce, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 480)
    - Shain, Rick, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 481)
    - Shake Records, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 482)
    - Shaw, John, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 483)
    - Shelley, Steve, undated (Box 7, Folder 484)
    - Sherwood, Jim, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 485)
    - Shimoto, Misao, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 486)
    - Shields, Sable (Sabel Starr), 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 486A)
    - Shirley, John, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 487)
    - Silliman, Ron, undated (Box 7, Folder 488)
    - Silverberg, Ira, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 489)
    - Simmonds, Harvey, undated (Box 7, Folder 490)
    - Smith, Peter, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 491)
    - Smyth, Patty, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 492)
    - Smyth-Meyers, Ruby, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 493)
    - Sollid, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 494)
    - Spake, Rebecca, 1991-1997 (Box 7, Folder 495)
    - Sparrow, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 496)
    - Springfield, Susan, 1978-1984 (Box 7, Folder 497)
    - Stander, Ava, 1983-1996 (Box 7, Folder 498)
    - Stone, Laura, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 499)
    - Stout, Robert Joe, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 500)
    - Stuart, Ken (Paragon House), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 501)
    - Sulchu, Radha, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 502)
    - Suvanjieff, Ivan, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 503)
    - Suzuki, Issei and Masue, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 504)
    - Szatmary, David, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 505)
    - Tager, Steven (Viking/Penguin), 1986 (Box 7, Folder 506)
    - Tagliabue, John, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 507)
    - Tanno, Jessica, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 508)
    - Tay, Steven, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 509)
    - Taylor, Tom, undated (Box 7, Folder 510)
    - Thau, Marty, undated (Box 7, Folder 511)
    - Thomajan, P.K., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 512)
    - Tish, George, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 513)
    - Tosches, Nick, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 514)
    - Transatlantic Review, undated (Box 7, Folder 515)
    - Trilnce, Anida Paply, 1981-1990 (Box 7, Folder 516)
    - Trinidad, David, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 517)
    - Van Dalen, Anton, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 518)
    - van der Helm, Alfred, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 519)
    - Vasellari, Rolf, 1986-1990 (Box 7, Folder 520)
    - Vaughan, Fra, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 521)
    - Venom, Vanessa, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 522)
    - Villar, E., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 523)
    - Vliet, R.G., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 524)
    - Valk, Kate, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 525)
    - Vreeland, undated (Box 7, Folder 526)
    - Wagner, Gary, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 527)
    - Wagner, Jon, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 528)
    - Waldman, Anne, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 529)
    - Walker, Sybil, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 530)
    - Ward, Marie, undated (Box 7, Folder 531)
    - Warner Brothers/Sire, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 532)
    - Wedding Invitations/List, undated (Box 7, Folder 533)
    - Weigel, T.B., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 534)
    - White, Jacqueline, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 535)
    - Williams, Bonnie, undated (Box 7, Folder 536)
    - Woodcock, Colin (Overground Records), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 537)
    - Wojewodzki, Richard, undated (Box 7, Folder 538)
    - Wolcott, Jim, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 539)
    - Wolfe, Linda, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 540)
    - Worthington, Rain, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 541)
    - Wylie, Andrew, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 542)
    - Wylie, Jennifer, undated (Box 7, Folder 543)
    - Yates, Paula, undated (Box 7, Folder 544)
    - Young, Marguerite, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 545)
    - Young, S. Kay, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 546)
    - Zavatsky, Bill, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 547)
    - Zermati, Marc, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 548)
    - Zodiak, Nick (Nick Zedd), undated (Box 8, Folder 549)
    - RH to partially identified correspondents, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 550)
    - Anonymous, undated (Box 8, Folder 551)
    - Partial Name before 1968, 1960-1968 (Box 8, Folder 552)
    - Partial Name, 1968-1974 (Box 8, Folder 553)
    - Partial Name, 1975-1979 (Box 8, Folder 554)
    - Partial Name, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 555)
    - Partial Name, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 556)
    - Partial Name, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 557)
    - Partial Name, 1980s (Box 8, Folder 558)
    - Partial Name, 1990-1994 (Box 8, Folder 559)
    - Partial Name, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 560)
    - Partial Name, 2000-2004 (Box 8, Folder 561)
    - Partial Name, 1990s-2000s (Box 8, Folder 562)
    - Correspondence between Carolyn Hodgson and Ernest Meyers, 1944-1947, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 563)
    - Fan Mail: Zines, 1978-1985 (Box 8, Folder 564)
    - Fan Mail: Rock and Roll, 1977-1983 (Box 8, Folder 565)
    - Fan Mail: from Bloody Mary, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 566)
    - Fan Mail: East Village Eye, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 567)
    - Fan Mail: from Japan, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 568)
  - Subseries B: Email Correspondence
    Consists of Richard Hell's professional and personal email correspondence from 1997-2003. As of September 2005, this material is in the process of being preserved and migrated for future access purposes.
- Series III: Projects
  SERIES III: Projects comprises materials related to producing and publicizing Richard Hell's individual artistic projects (albums, books, films, etc.). Each project is arranged as a subseries with projects ordered chronologically by date of completion.
  - Subseries A: Genesis: Grasp
    Materials relating to Richard Hell's first publishing imprint; contains correspondence, manuscripts, production files and business records.
    - Description of Materials, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 569)
    - Correspondence - CCLM, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 570)
    - Correspondence - Distributors, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 571)
    - Correspondence - Out of Sight, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 571A)
    - Correspondence - Printing Products, undated (Box 8, Folder 572)
    - Copyright Registration, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 573)
    - Business Records, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 574)
    - Tom Miller and Richard Meyers, The 99 Beautiful, Names of Allah, undated (Box 8, Folder 575)
    - Simon Schuchat, Svelte, supplement to #5/6., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 576)
    - Ernie Stomach: Typeface Design, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 577)
    - Genesis: Grasp #1, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 578)
    - Genesis: Grasp #2, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 579)
    - Genesis: Grasp #3, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 580)
    - Genesis: Grasp #4, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 581)
    - Yuki Hartman, A One of Me (supplement to #4), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 582)
    - Genesis: Grasp #5/6, undated (Box 8, Folder 583)
    - Ernie Stomach, Uh (supplement to #5/6), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 584)
  - Subseries B: Dot Books
    Materials relating to Richard Hell's second publishing imprint; contains correspondence, production files and business records.
    - Letterhead designs, undated (Box 8, Folder 585)
    - Manuscript pages, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 586)
    - Andrew Wylie, envelope, undated (Box 8, Folder 587)
    - Andrew Wylie, undated (Box 8, Folder 588)
    - Andrew Wylie, Yellow Flowers (Layout), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 588)
    - Andrew Wylie, Yellow Flowers (Materials), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 589)
    - Andrew Wylie, Yellow Flowers notebook mock-up, undated (Box 9, Folder 590)
    - Andrew Wylie, Yellow Flowers material from notebook mock-up, undated (Box 9, Folder 591)
    - Andrew Wylie, Yellow Flowers Book, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 592)
    - Tom Verlaine, 28th Century (envelope), undated (Box 9, Folder 593)
    - Tom Verlaine, 28th Century (manuscripts and materials), undated (Box 9, Folder 594)
    - Tom Verlaine, 28th Century (photos and mock-up), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 595)
    - Patti Smith, Merde (materials), undated (Box 9, Folder 596)
    - Shot Books, Logo Design, undated (Box 9, Folder 597)
    - Annie Hickman, Marilyn Monroe, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 597A)
  - Subseries C: Wanna Go Out?
    Materials relating to the production of Wanna Go Out? a collaborative volume of poetry authored by Richard Hell and Tom Verlaine under the pseudonym Theresa Stern.
    - Manuscript Box, undated (Box 9, Folder 598)
    - Poems from box, undated (Box 9, Folder 599)
    - Poems, undated (Box 9, Folder 600)
    - Manuscripts, undated (Box 9, Folder 601)
    - Cover Letters to Publishers, undated (Box 9, Folder 602)
    - Rejection Letters, undated (Box 9, Folder 603)
    - Pages, undated (Box 9, Folder 604)
    - Author Photos, undated (Box 9, Folder 605)
    - Photo Invoice, undated (Box 9, Folder 606)
    - Layout, undated (Box 9, Folder 607)
    - Wayside Gardens Catalog, undated (Box 9, Folder 608)
    - Book w/ ms notes and corrections, undated (Box 9, Folder 609)
    - Book, undated (Box 9, Folder 610)
    - Invoice from USC Library, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 611)
    - Orders, undated (Box 9, Folder 612)
    - Copyright Inquiry and Reply, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 613)
    - Copyright certificate, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 614)
    - Note from Nicole, undated (Box 9, Folder 615)
    - Reviews, undated (Box 9, Folder 616)
    - Photos from folder, undated (Box 9, Folder 617)
    - Punk Interview MS, undated (Box 9, Folder 618)
    - Interview with Theresa Stern, Punk #4, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 619)
    - Poem in Punk 5, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 620)
    - Wanna Go Out? (French), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 621)
  - Subseries D: Television
    Materials related to Richard Hell's role in Television.
    - Band Biographical notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 622)
    - Promotional Materials, undated (Box 9, Folder 623)
    - Design Elements, undated (Box 9, Folder 624)
    - Clippings - Soho Weekly News, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 625)
    - Soho Weekly News, Patti Smith "Television: Escapees from Heaven", 1974 (Box 9, Folder 626)
    - Rock Scene, Patti Smith, "Someone Somewhere Must Stand Naked", 1974 (Box 9, Folder 627)
    - Clipping, Andy Warhol's Interview, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 628)
  - Subseries E: Heartbreakers
    Materials relating to Richard Hell's role in the Heartbreakers.
    - Clipping, Hit Parader #134, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 629)
    - Clipping, Newsmagazine, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 630)
    - Clipping, Rock News #1, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 631)
    - Interview, Rock News #2, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 631A)
    - New York Rocker 1.1, Theresa Stern "Tales of the Heartbreakers", 1976 (Box 9, Folder 632)
    - Images, Rock Scene 4.2, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 633)
    - Clipping, New Musical Express, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 634)
    - Interview, Punk 1.3, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 635)
    - Clipping, Musicians Classified, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 636)
    - Rock Scene "Heartbreakers Rock the Blank Generation", 1976 (Box 9, Folder 637)
    - Clipping, "Why I love the Heartbreakers", undated (Box 9, Folder 638)
    - Clipping, "Heartbreakers" by Craig Gholson, undated (Box 9, Folder 639)
    - Sabel Starr MS, undated (Box 9, Folder 640)
  - Subseries F: Richard Hell and the Voidoids, Blank Generation
    Materials relating to the production, publicity and marketing of the Voidoids first album.
    - Flyer, undated (Box 9, Folder 641)
    - Production Materials, undated (Box 9, Folder 642)
    - Copyright, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 643)
    - Concert Photos, undated (Box 9, Folder 644)
    - Hell biographical note, undated (Box 9, Folder 645)
    - Clipping, Alan Betrock, undated (Box 9, Folder 646)
    - Promotional Materials, undated (Box 9, Folder 647)
    - Unidentified Clippings, undated (Box 9, Folder 648)
    - Misc. Clippings, undated (Box 9, Folder 649)
    - Rock News International #7, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 650)
    - Clipping, Sounds, New Wave Chart, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 651)
    - Clipping, Foxtrot, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 652)
    - High Times #18, Punk Insert, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 653)
    - Cheap Thrills 3.10, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 654)
    - Big Star #1, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 655)
    - MS concert review by Susan Springfield, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 656)
    - New Haven Register, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 657)
    - New York City Tuesday Night #3, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 658)
    - New York City Tuesday Night #4, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 659)
    - Commercial Appeal, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 660)
    - review, Record World, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 661)
    - review, Jungleland, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 662)
    - New York City Tuesday Night #6, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 663)
    - review, New Musical Express, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 664)
    - review, Sounds (partial), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 665)
    - U.K. Tour schedule, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 665A)
    - review, Unicorn Times, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 666)
    - clipping, Sounds, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 667)
    - review, Creem 9.7, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 668)
    - clipping, Sounds New Wave Chart, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 669)
    - Music Life (Japan), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 670)
    - clipping, New Musical Express, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 671)
    - clipping, New Musical Express, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 672)
    - clipping, New Musical Express, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 673)
    - interview, Zig Zag #81, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 674)
    - Punk #12, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 675)
    - clipping, Liberation (French), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 676)
    - Tour review, PMM #26, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 677)
    - Tour itinerary w/Elvis Costello, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 678)
    - clipping, New Musical Express, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 679)
    - clipping, Sounds, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 680)
    - Shake records press release, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 680A)
    - Musician, Lester Bangs, "Rock in the Seventies", 1980 (Box 10, Folder 681)
    - clipping, Village Voice, Lester Bangs, "John Lennon is Alive and a Voidoid", 1981 (Box 10, Folder 682)
    - clipping, NY Daily News CD release, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 683)
    - clipping, New York Times, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 684)
    - Time Out New York #178, New York's Greatest Hits", 1999 (Box 10, Folder 685)
    - clippings, CD re-release, undated (Box 10, Folder 686)
    - clipping, The Wire # 193, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 687)
    - Spin, 50 Most Essential Punk Albums, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 688)
    - Vanity Fair, Beck's 50 favorite album covers, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 689)
  - Subseries G: Final Reward
    Materials relating to the production of the film Final Reward.
    - Script with ms notes by RH, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 690)
    - Shooting schedule, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 691)
    - Photographs, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 692)
  - Subseries H: Blank Generation (film)
    Materials relating to the production of the film Blank Generation.
    - Rock News International #3, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 693)
    - RH notes on shooting, undated (Box 10, Folder 694)
    - Notes and materials, undated (Box 10, Folder 695)
    - Script Pages, undated (Box 10, Folder 696)
    - Legal correspondence, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 697)
    - Invoice, A, Richard Golub, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 698)
    - Power of Attorney, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 699)
    - press, Vogue, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 700)
    - press, Rock Scene, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 701)
  - Subseries I: 1980 Road Trip
    Materials from Richard's drive across the country in 1980 with Roberta Bayley. These notes later became source material for Go Now.
    - Roadtrip, Small Notebook, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 702)
    - Journal "Triptik", 1980 (Box 10, Folder 703)
    - Materials from "Triptik", undated (Box 10, Folder 704)
    - Manuscripts, undated (Box 10, Folder 705)
    - 1980 Roadtrip, Photographs, photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box 10, Folder 706)
    - Polaroids, undated (Box 10, Folder 707)
    - Cadillac Sale Information, undated (Box 10, Folder 708)
    - Receipt, undated (Box 10, Folder 709)
    - Hearst Castle, undated (Box 10, Folder 710)
    - Iola Burgraff, undated (Box 10, Folder 711)
    - Fresh and Firm film treatments, undated (Box 10, Folder 712)
    - Newspapers, undated (Box 10, Folder 713)
    - Images of Cadillacs, undated (Box 10, Folder 714)
    - East Village Eye article, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 715)
    - Go Now, Chapter 5, undated (Box 10, Folder 716)
    - Cannibalized Go Now, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 717)
  - Subseries J: Richard Hell and the Voidoids, Destiny Street
    Materials relating to the production, publicity and marketing of the Voidoids second album.
    - Liner Notes (proof), undated (Box 10, Folder 718)
    - Press Release, Jem/Red Star Records, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 719)
    - Trouser Press # 78, #79, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 720)
    - Review, NY Times, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 721)
    - Review, Washington Post, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 722)
    - U.S. Tour, L.A. Reader, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 723)
    - Review, Rockerilla #26, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 724)
    - Clipping, New York Rocker, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 725)
    - Musician #49, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 726)
    - NY Times, "10 Best of 82", 1982 (Box 10, Folder 727)
    - NY Times, New Years Eve concert, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 728)
    - Clippings and correspondence, Jem Records, undated (Box 10, Folder 729)
    - Clipping, U.S. Tour, The Eagle, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 730)
    - Interview, New Musical Express, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 731)
    - Review, The Face #36, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 732)
    - Clipping (in French), undated (Box 10, Folder 733)
    - clipping, San Francisco Chronicle /Examiner, undated (Box 10, Folder 734)
    - Singer Management Press Sheet, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 735)
  - Subseries K: Smithereens
    Materials relating to Richard Hell's role in the Susan Seidelman film, Smithereens.
    - Poster Contract, undated (Box 10, Folder 736)
    - Invitations, undated (Box 10, Folder 737)
    - Ads (designed by RH, undated (Box 10, Folder 738)
    - Reviews, undated (Box 10, Folder 739)
    - Interview, Bop Eye #2, undated (Box 10, Folder 740)
  - Subseries L: Nick Zedd
    Materials relating to Richard Hell's work with filmmaker Nick Zedd.
    - The Deprogramming, treatment, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 741)
    - The Deprogramming, script with RH Ms. Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 742)
    - Geek Maggot Bingo, flyers and review, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 743)
    - Geek Maggot Bingo, Photographs, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 744)
    - The Wild World of Lydia Lunch, undated (Box 10, Folder 745)
  - Subseries M: RIP
    Materials relating to Richard Hell's collection of Voidoids outtakes, RIP.
    - Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 746)
    - Liner Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 747)
    - Press Release, ROIR Records, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 748)
    - Track Listing and Lyrics, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 749)
    - Reviews / Clippings, undated (Box 10, Folder 750)
  - Subseries N: Heroin Research
    Materials relating to research and composition of Richard Hell's articles on heroin use from 1986 to 1996.
    - Heroin Notebook, undated (Box 10, Folder 751)
    - Material from Notebook, undated (Box 10, Folder 752)
    - MS, Notes on Junk/Rock, undated (Box 10, Folder 753)
    - MS, Heroin in England, undated (Box 10, Folder 754)
    - Opium and the People, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 755)
    - The Drug User, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 756)
    - Guide to the Met 3: Drug Squad, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 757)
    - Big Deal, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 758)
    - Hep-Cats, Narcs, and Pipe Dreams, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 759)
    - Scoring Smack, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 760)
    - Opium Poppy Cultivation, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 761)
    - On Heroin, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 762)
    - Can a War on Drugs Succeed?, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 763)
    - Surveys and Statistics on Drug Taking in Britain, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 764)
    - The Heroin Solution, undated (Box 11, Folder 765)
    - Street Drugs, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 766)
    - Drugs Unlimited, undated (Box 11, Folder 767)
    - Drug, Set, and Setting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 768)
  - Subseries O: Poetry Readings
    Materials relating to Richard Hell's poetry readings, including notes from his tenure as the coordinator of the Monday Night Poetry series at the Poetry Project.
    - Reading Notes, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 769)
    - Poetry Project Monday Readings, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 770)
    - Reading for Cookie Mueller's funeral, undated (Box 11, Folder 770A)
    - Reading at Old Dominion University, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 771)
    - Responses, undated (Box 11, Folder 772)
  - Subseries P: CUZ
    Files relating to the production of each issue of Richard Hell's literary journal, includes correspondence and manuscripts.
    - Correspondence, Ameen, Mark, undated (Box 11, Folder 773)
    - Correspondence, Andrews, Bruce, undated (Box 11, Folder 774)
    - Correspondence, Ashbury, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 775)
    - Correspondence, Brodey, Jim, undated (Box 11, Folder 776)
    - Correspondence, Bristol, Bobby, undated (Box 11, Folder 777)
    - Correspondence, Budget Committee, undated (Box 11, Folder 778)
    - Correspondence, Carter, Ellen, undated (Box 11, Folder 779)
    - Correspondence, DeCapite, Mike, undated (Box 11, Folder 780)
    - Correspondence, Deering, Donald, undated (Box 11, Folder 781)
    - Correspondence, Dlugos, Tim, undated (Box 11, Folder 782)
    - Correspondence, Dubris, Maggie, undated (Box 11, Folder 783)
    - Correspondence, Equi, Eaine, undated (Box 11, Folder 784)
    - Correspondence, Hell, Richard, undated (Box 11, Folder 785)
    - Correspondence, Highfill, Mitch, undated (Box 11, Folder 786)
    - Correspondence, Killian, Kevin, undated (Box 11, Folder 787)
    - Correspondence, Krawiec, Richard, undated (Box 11, Folder 788)
    - Correspondence, Lyons, Kim, undated (Box 11, Folder 789)
    - Correspondence, Myles, Eileen, undated (Box 11, Folder 790)
    - Correspondence, Ratcliffe, Stephen, undated (Box 11, Folder 791)
    - Correspondence, Richie, Eugene, undated (Box 11, Folder 792)
    - Correspondence, Russakoff, Molly, undated (Box 11, Folder 793)
    - Correspondence, Sala Jerome, undated (Box 11, Folder 794)
    - Correspondence, Sparrow, undated (Box 11, Folder 795)
    - Correspondence, Timmons, Suzie, undated (Box 11, Folder 796)
    - Correspondence, Trinidad, David, undated (Box 11, Folder 797)
    - Correspondence, William Burroughs communications, undated (Box 11, Folder 798)
    - Correspondence, Yau, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 799)
    - Correspondence, Fan Mail, undated (Box 11, Folder 800)
    - Correspondence, Partial Name, undated (Box 11, Folder 801)